Set CHROME_PATH and APIKEY in settings.py accordingly!
MAXRESULTS sets a limit for the ammount of video upload data that can be retrieved from one channel.

You can create a throwaway email to register on youtube and then create an APIKEY for the application. 
APIKEY creation guide: https://developers.google.com/youtube/v3/getting-started

The requests library is needed for this script!
If you have pip installed you only need to run the "requestslib_pip_setup" batch file.
You can also manually donwload the library here: https://github.com/requests/requests

If you don't like being signed up 24/7 on google and don't care too much about playlists, then 
this is a good alternative that notifies you whenever your favorit youtubers upload something.


Made by:
Shikata ga nai 仕方が無い